虚幻勇士冒险 S2E2 重逢 由özberk özen制作
视频来源：https://youtu.be/Znm87ghp_K0，中文字幕由熙洛Chincode制作，翻译：jky，Albeta
Previously on Code Lyoko Adventures
虚幻勇士冒险前情提要
OK, Franz Hopper goes to the tower!
好了 Franz Hopper去了圆塔
I will use Code Franz.
我将使用代码Franz
OK. Here we go. Code Franz.
好的 来吧 代码Franz
Jeremy, bring me back on earth now.
Jeremy 现在把我带回地球
I need to be in the scanner room.
我需要到扫描室去
OK, Aelita.
好的 Aelita
I can't believe this, it's actually working.
难以置信 这真的起作用了
Father.
父亲
I missed you so much.
我太想你了
I missed you too, sweetheart.
我也想你 亲爱的
Oh Aelita, I missed you so much.
哦 Aelita 我太想你了
Is this real, Aelita? After all these years.
这是真的吗 Aelita？这么多年过去了
It is, father.
是的 父亲
Come on now. Let's go upstairs and see Jeremy.
现在来吧 让我们上楼去看看Jeremy
OK, sweetheart.
好的 亲爱的
It worked. I can't believe this.
它成功了 我真不敢相信
Guys, mission accomplished, now let's destroy that supercomputer.
伙计们 任务完成了 现在我们来摧毁那台超级计算机吧
Nice to meet you, welcome to earth, Franz Hopper.
很高兴见到你 欢迎来到地球 Franz Hopper
Nice to meet you too, Jeremy Belpois.
我也很高兴见到你 Jeremy Belpois
Thanks to you, I'm back on earth again. I'm eternal grateful.
多亏了你们 我又回到了地球上 感激不尽
Yoho Einstein, we're in the supercomputer room now.
哟 爱因斯坦 我们现在在超级计算机室了
What should we do?
我们应该怎么做？
You can now destroy the supercomputer, Lyoko Warriors.
你现在可以摧毁超级计算机了 Lyoko战士们
Ulrich, is the tower still there?
Ulrich 圆塔还在那里吗？
Yes, the tower is still here...but wait.
是的 圆塔还在这里......但是等等
Something is happening
有问题
What on earth is that?
那到底是什么？
What is happening.
发生了什么事
Ah the tower disappeared.
啊 那座塔消失了
Uh, Franz Hopper, I think we have a very big and beautiful problem here.
呃 Franz Hopper 我想我们有一个又大又美丽的问题
What? What's happening?
什么？发生什么事了？
There are really strange signals here.
这里产生了一些非常奇怪的信号
I don't even know how to explain it, some kind of cables strike the ground into this tower under it.
我甚至不知道该怎么解释 圆塔下方的地面里钻出某种电缆 袭击了圆塔
What is happening?
发生了什么事？
Now there are some strange lights in the sky
现在天空中出现了一些奇怪的光
What? How can XANA be able to do that?
什么 XANA怎么能做到这一点呢？
Now he can control the earth too?
现在他也能控制地球了？
That's impossible!
这是不可能的！
I mean, if we destroy the supercomputer now, I'm sure it'll affect his powers.
我的意思是 如果我们现在破坏超级计算机 肯定会影响他的能力
Yeah, and make it fast too.
是的 而且要尽快
The supercomputer is making a strange noise.
超级计算机正在发出奇怪的声音
What? Odd, Yumi, destroy it now!
什么？Odd Yumi 现在就毁掉它
OK Franz, Yumi are you ready to destroy it?
好的Franz Yumi你准备好摧毁它了吗？
Of course to my signal.
当然准备好了 听我的信号
3 2 1.
NOW.
就现在
Odd, wake up.
Odd 醒醒
Sector alpha is starting to destroy itself.
阿尔法区开始自我毁灭了
Odd, Odd, can you-
Odd Odd 你能-
Relax Einstein, I'm awake.
没事 爱因斯坦 我已经醒了
I'm getting out of here right now.
我现在要离开这里了
Goodbye XANA!
再见XANA！
Here it is.
给你
Thank you, have a really nice day!
谢谢你 祝好
Hi Aelita!
嗨 Aelita
Hi Yumi!
嗨 Yumi
I just bought some food for my father.
我刚刚给我父亲买了些食物
I guess he's really hungry right now.
我猜他现在真的很饿
Good idea, nice thought.
好主意
He probablity doesn't eat in years now, Aelita.
他可能已经好几年没吃东西了 Aelita
Thanks, and after that we're going to the hermitage to see our old house.
谢谢 之后我们要去隐居之所 看看我们的老房子
What do you plan to do with your father?
你对你父亲有什么计划？
Do you know where he is going to live?
你知道他要去哪里住吗？
I don't really know, I think it is going be a problem.
我真的不知道 我想这会是一个问题
Yumi, what should I do?
Yumi 我应该怎么做？
Sorry but I can't help you on this.
对不起 我帮不了你
And I have to go now, I'm so sorry.
而且我现在要走了 很抱歉
See you later!
回头见！
Oh, OK. See ya!
哦 好的 再见！
It feels very weird when you see the environment again.
当你再次看到地球的环境时 会感觉到非常奇怪
Everything looks so different.
一切看起来都那么不同
The buildings, the cars, everything.
建筑物 汽车 所有的一切
I haven't seen the sunlight for so long.
我已经很久没有看到阳光了
I forgot how clear the weather is.
我忘了天气是多么的晴朗
Walking on the street.
走在大街上
Everything seems so weird.
一切都显得那么奇怪
But I realized something, I really missed Earth.
但我意识到一件事 我真的很怀念地球
You'll get used to it, Dad, like I did.
你会习惯的 爸爸 就像我一样
When I first came back to earth, everything was so different but Jeremy was there for me.
当我第一次回到地球时 一切都那么不同 但Jeremy在那里等我
Oh I think I get the picture.
哦 我想我明白了
Tell me something, sweetheart. You and Jeremy-
告诉我一些事情 亲爱的 你和Jeremy-
What? What happened to the hermitage?
什么？隐居之所怎么了？
This can't be the house I bought.
这不可能是我买的那个房子
I remember when I bought it.
我记得我买下它的时候
I remember the last day with you.
我记得和你在一起的最后一天
It was not like this.
它不是这样的
Daddy!
爸爸
The men in black are here.
黑衣人来了
I know, do you know where Mr. Puck is?
我知道 你知道帕克先生在哪里吗？
Yeah.
是的
Come on, Aelita. Quick.
来吧 Aelita 快
Fast, Aelita!
快 Aelita
Fast.
快
Come on, Aelita. Quick.
来吧 Aelita 快
There is no time to lose.
没有时间可以浪费了
Come on. Come on.
来吧 来吧
That day they were there to kidnap you and kill me.
那天 他们在那里打算绑了你 然后杀了我
I'm so sorry, Aelita!
我很抱歉 Aelita
It's OK, father! Let's go inside!
没事的 父亲 我们进去吧
OK, sweetie, let's go.
好了 亲爱的 我们走吧
Inside is worse than outside.
里面比外面更糟糕
What happened to our home?
我们的家怎么了？
Look what I found, father...It's incredible!
看我发现了什么 父亲 太不可思议了
What's the matter, Aelita?
怎么了 Aelita？
Is everything OK?
一切都好吗？
Oh I remember the day we took this photo.
哦 我记得我们拍这张照片的那天
I remember that day too.
我也记得那一天
I- I really miss my mother
我--我真的很想念我的母亲
Dad, I miss her so much
爸爸 我很想她
Me too, sweetheart.
我也是 亲爱的
Me too.
我也是
Anyway, let's go to the factory, Dad.
不管怎样 我们去工厂吧 爸爸
OK, Aelita!
好的 Aelita